Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Sandburg, Carl
    - Permissions and royalty statements
      - Alphabetical
        - Sayers, Frances Clarke, and Weston Woods Studios, 1985-1986
        - Shanks, Robert, 1979
        - Shawnee Press, and Earl Robinson, 1962-1963, undated
        - Silver Burdett Co., 1978-1986
        - Steel Mill Productions, 1983
        - Stewart, Frederick, 1963, undated
        - Wade, Stephen, 1979-1980, undated
        - Walton Music Corp., 1971-1983
        - Warren, Elinor Remick, 1945-1954, 1975-1986, undated
        - Wolper Productions, 1963
      - Chronological
        - 1960-1962, (2 folders)
        - 1963-1966, (8 folders) (Box 621)
        - 1967-1969, (7 folders) (Box 622)
        - 1970
          - Jan.-June
          - July-Dec. (Box 623)
        - 1971-1972, (6 folders)
        - 1973-1977, (8 folders) (Box 624)
        - 1978-1991, (9 folders) (Box 625)
        - 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box 626)
    - Public appearances
      - Address on Lincoln Day, Joint Session of Congress, Washington, D.C., 1959
      - An Evening with Carl Sandburg, State Department, Washington, D.C., 1961-1962
      - Exhibit on Centennial of the Civil War, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C., 1961-1962, undated
      - Founders Day Dinner, Arizona State University, Tempe, Ariz.
        - 1963-1964
      - Gettysburg National Cemetery, Gettysburg, Pa., 1959
      - A Lincoln Portrait, Philharmonic Hall, New York, N.Y., 1962-1963, undated
      - The One Hundredth Anniversary of the Inaugural of Abraham Lincoln, Washington, D.C.
        - Correspondence and notes, 1961-1962
        - Printed matter, 1961
        - Text of speech, 1961
    - Rootabaga Stories
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1966, 1974-1993, undated
      - Miscellany, 1974, 1985-1988, undated
      - Notes, 1963-1975, 1981-1992, undated
      - Typescript, 1988 (Box 627)
    - Sandburg's Lincoln
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1981
      - Notes, 1972-1979, undated
      - Photograph, undated See Oversize
      - Printed matter, 1973-1979, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1973-1990, (2 folders)
      - Scripts and shooting schedules (Box 628)
        - “Crossing Fox River,” 1974
        - “The Last Days,” 1974
        - “Lincoln, The Unwilling Warrior,” 1974
        - “Mrs. Lincoln's Husband,” 1974
        - “Prairie Lawyer,” 1974
        - “Sad Figure Laughing,” 1974
        - “Within Sight of Canaan,” 1974
    - The Seeking Mind, 1961-1962, undated
    - Sound recordings (Box 629)
      - American Airlines
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1959
        - Miscellany, 1959
      - American Telephone and Telegraph Co., 1962
      - Columbia Records
        - Flat Rock Ballads and A Lincoln Portrait, 1957-1961
        - Man's Family of Song, 1960-1962
        - Rodgers and Hammerstein Gala Album, 1960-1961, undated
    - The Tall American: Gary Cooper, 1963
    - Television appearances
      - “Bell Telephone Hour”
        - 1960, Feb.
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1959-1960
          - Notes and printed matter, 1959-1960, undated
        - 1962, Nov.
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1962, undated
          - Notes and printed matter, 1962
          - Script, 1962
      - “CBS Reports”
        - “The Best of Sandburg,” 1966-1969
        - “Carl Sandburg of Gettysburg”
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1961, 1967-1969, 1977
          - Notes and printed matter, 1959-1962, undated
          - Scripts, 1961
        - “Carl Sandburg; Lincoln's Prairie Years,” 1961-1962
        - “The Supreme Court,” 1962-1963 (Box 630)
      - “Dinah Shore Show,” 1964
      - “The Ed Sullivan Show”
        - 1962
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1961-1962
          - Notes and scripts, 1961-1962
        - 1967
      - “Gene Kelly Spectacular”
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1959-1960
        - Miscellany, 1959-1960, undated
      - “Meet the Press,” 1959
    - Works about Sandburg
      - Adato, Perry Miller, and Paul Shyre, Carl Sandburg: Echoes and Silences
        - Correspondence, 1978-1982
        - List and notes, 1979-1982, undated
        - Photographs and printed matter, 1982-1983, undated
        - Proposal, 1979
        - Scripts, 1981, (2 folders)
        - Transcripts, undated, (2 folders) (Box 631)
        - Treatment, undated
        - Trip to North Carolina, 1978, undated
      - Coronet Instructional Films, Carl Sandburg Discusses His Work and Carl Sandburg Discusses Lincoln, 1954-1966, undated
      - Corwin, Norman, The World of Carl Sandburg
        - Play
          - Amateur and stock rights
            - 1961-1979, (5 folders)
            - 1980-1985 (Box 632)
          - Contracts, 1959-1960, undated
          - Correspondence, 1958-1961, undated, (6 folders)
          - Financial records, 1959-1960, 1970
          - Itineraries, 1960, undated
          - Notes, 1959-1963, undated, (3 folders) (Box 633)
          - Printed matter
            - Henry Miller's Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1960, undated
            - Miscellany, 1959-1960, undated
          - Scripts, 1960, undated, (2 folders)
        - Publications
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1959-1962
          - Notes, 1960-1962, undated
          - Printed matter, 1961-1962, undated (Box 634)
          - Royalty statements, 1962-1971
        - Television film, 1959-1978, 1985-1988, undated
      - d'Alessio, Gregory, On the Light Side with Carl Sandburg
        - 1967-1971, undated
      - Golden, Harry, Carl Sandburg, 1961, undated
      - Mitgang, Herbert, The Letters of Carl Sandburg, 1966-1973, undated
      - National Educational Television, “NET Festival, Carl Sandburg Remembered,” 1968, undated
      - Niven, Penelope, Carl Sandburg: A Biography
        - Bibliography, 1984, undated
        - Condensed text, undated
        - Miscellany, 1982, undated
        - Proposal to Atheneum/Macmillan Co., 1989 (Box 635)
        - Proposal to Kroll, undated
      - Sadler, Tish, Strong Men Keep Coming On, undated
      - Steichen, Edward, Photographers View of Carl Sandburg, 1966, undated
      - Steichen, Paula, Hyacinths and Biscuits, undated
  - Sandler, Ake, 1962-1963, undated
  - Sankowich, Lee, 1988-1989
  - Sanza, Enrique
    - Correspondence
      - 1969-1970
      - 1971-1973, undated (Box 636)
    - Notes, 1970-1971, undated
    - Printed matter, 1970-1971, undated
  - Sapp, Jo, undated
  - Sarabhai, Mrinalini, 1947-1948
  - Satterwhite, Anne B., 1975, 1991-1992
  - Saunders, Lorna, 1974-1978, undated
  - Sayers, Michael
    - Box office receipts, 1947-1948
    - Contracts, 1947-1948
    - Correspondence
      - 1946-1947, (4 folders)
      - 1948-1955, 1964, undated, (2 folders) (Box 637)
    - Notes, 1947-1948, undated
    - Photographs, undated
    - Printed matter, 1947-1948, undated
    - Script, 1948
    - Synopses, undated
  - Scammell, Henry, 1995
  - Scanlon, Julienne Marie, 1986-1987
  - Schafer, Milton, 1956-1958
  - Schechter, Marshall D.
    - Correspondence, 1961-1971
    - Miscellany, 1960-1970, undated
  - Schiffman, Jack, 1978-1980
  - Schloss, Gilbert A., 1973-1977
  - Schmeck, Harold M.
    - Book proposals, 1984, undated
    - Contract, 1981
    - Correspondence, 1969, 1980-1989
    - Notes, 1980-1989, undated (Box 638)
    - Printed matter, 1981-1989, undated, (2 folders)
  - Schneider, Alan
    - The Circus of Dr. Lao, 1957, undated
    - Cry of Victory, 1960, undated
    - Dealer's Choice, 1959, undated
    - Endgame
      - Contracts, 1957
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959, undated
      - Financial records, 1958-1975
      - Notes, 1957-1958, undated
      - Printed matter, 1958
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1956, undated
    - Kataki, 1958-1959
    - Krapp's Last Tape and The Zoo Story, 1959-1960, undated
    - Lovely Star, Good Night, 1958-1959, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1955-1960
      - Correspondence, 1955-1961, 1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 639)
      - Notes, 1956-1960, undated
      - Printed matter, 1956-1961, 1984, undated
    - Miss Lonelyhearts, 1956-1957, undated
    - “Omnibus,” 1956-1958, undated
    - The Rape of the Belt, 1960, undated
    - The Secret Concubine, 1959
    - The Secret of Freedom, 1959, undated
    - The Summer of the 17th Doll, 1958-1960, undated, (2 folders)
    - Trees of Promise, 1957-1958, undated
    - Twelve Angry Men, 1960
    - Two for the Seesaw, 1960
    - Waiting for Godot, 1960
    - Warner Brothers Studio, 1957
  - Schneider, Benno (Box 640)
    - Box office receipts, 1947-1948, (3 folders)
    - Contracts, 1947-1948, undated
    - Correspondence, 1947-1952, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1947-1948, undated
  - Schneier, Monroe, 1961-1969, undated
  - Schoendoerffer, Pierre
    - The Anderson Platoon
      - Contracts, 1964-1968, 1978, 1987-1991
      - Correspondence, 1967-1970, 1978-1991, undated, (3 folders)
      - Notes, 1967-1968, 1978-1981, 1987-1989, undated
      - Printed matter, 1967-1968, 1989-1992, undated (Box 641)
      - Royalty statements, 1967-1989, undated, (5 folders)
    - Farewell to the King
      - Contract, 1968
      - Correspondence, 1967-1970, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1967-1970, undated
      - Printed matter, 1969-1970 (Box 642)
      - Treatments, 1969, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contract, 1987
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968, 1987-1992, undated
      - Notes, 1966-1970, 1984, undated
    - Reminiscences, 1991-1992, undated
  - Schonberg, Harold C.
    - Facing the Music
      - Contracts, 1979-1981
      - Correspondence, 1979-1981, undated
      - Draft, circa 1981, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 643)
      - Notes, 1979-1981, undated
      - Printed matter, 1981
      - Proofs, 1981
    - The Great Conductors, 1984-1986, undated
    - The Great Pianists from Mozart to the Present, 1980-1993, undated
    - Horowitz: His Life and Music
      - Contracts, 1986-1990
      - Correspondence, 1986-1993, undated
      - Notes, 1986-1992, undated (Box 644)
      - Printed matter, 1986-1993
      - Typescripts, 1987-1991
    - Lectures, 1980-1988, undated
    - Lives of the Great Composers, 1966, 1981-1984, undated
    - Lives of the Great Performers, 1982-1984
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1973-1993, undated
      - Notes, 1979-1989, undated
      - Photograph, 1981
      - Printed matter, 1973-1989, undated
    - The Virtuosi (formerly titled The Glorious Ones ), 1985-1988, undated
  - Schuman, William
    - Correspondence, 1968-1974, 1983, 1992, undated
    - Notes, 1968-1974, undated
    - Printed matter, 1963-1974, 1983-1986, 1992
  - Schwartz, Joel
    - Free Games, 1970-1971
    - Just a Quiet Note, 1964
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and notes, 1965-1976, undated
    - My Eye Sees Not So Far, 1964-1967, undated (Box 645)
    - Pinball Machine, Slivovitz, and Tilt (formerly titled Untilted ) See also same container, Visions and Revisions
      - Contracts, 1969-1970, 1981
      - Correspondence, 1967-1974, 1981, 1988, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1969-1970, 1981, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1971-1986
    - Psalms of Two Davids, 1969-1973, undated
    - Ripe Tripe, 1971-1972, undated
    - Sitting Ducks
      - Miscellany, 1976, undated
      - Typescript, 1976
    - Touch, 1966, undated
    - Untitled, 1964-1965
    - Visions and Revisions See also same container, Pinball Machine, Slivovitz, and Tilt (formerly titled Untilted )
  - Schwartz, Jonathan, 1985 (Box 646)
  - Schwartz, Paula, 1978
  - Schwarz, Robin, 1986-1988, undated
  - Schweitzer, S. S. (“Paddy”), 1955-1956, undated
  - Schwerin, Doris, 1978
  - Sciascia, Armando, 1984-1985
  - Scott, Alan Robert
    - Apollo and Miss Agnes
      - Contracts, 1957-1963
      - Correspondence, 1957-1967, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1957-1967, undated
      - Printed matter, 1963-1967, undated
      - Script, 1963
    - Attention World, undated
    - Conflict of Interest, 1976-1977, undated (Box 647)
    - Cricket Smith, 1959-1962, undated
    - Eden Again? 1969-1970, undated
    - Every Tuesday and Thursday, 1962-1963
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1959-1968, 1977, undated
      - Notes, 1959-1961, 1968, 1976-1977, undated
    - What Price Exclusivity? 1960-1961, undated
  - Seawell, Brock, 1972
  - Sekoff, Roy, 1983-1989, undated
  - Self, Edwin B., 1971, undated
  - Shaktman, Benjamin, 1991
  - Shalala, Donna E., 1987-1989
  - Shames, Priscilla, 1970-1972, undated
  - Shanes, Eric, 1992, undated
  - Shange, Ntozake
    - Balm in Gilead, 1985-1986
    - BBC-TV, London, England, 1985-1986, undated
    - Betsey Brown (Box 648)
      - American Music Theatre Festival, Philadelphia, Pa., 1988-1991, undated
      - Crossroads Theatre Company, New Brunswick, N.J., 1992-1994
      - Film offers, 1985-1988, undated
      - McCarter Theatre Company, Princeton, N.J.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1986-1991, undated
        - Printed matter, 1991, undated
      - Miscellany, 1983-1988, undated
      - New York Shakespeare Festival, New York, N.Y., 1983-1989, undated
      - Scripts
        - 1982
        - 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 649)
    - Billie Holiday's Life Story, 1980-1986, undated
    - Boogie Woogie Landscapes, 1983-1985, undated
    - Creation for Liberation, 1987-1989, undated See also Oversize
    - Educating Rita
      - Miscellany, 1982-1986
      - Script, undated
    - Everyday Death, 1985, undated
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow Is Enuf, 1984-1988
    - From Okra to Greens/A Different Kinda Love Story, 1983
    - I Heard Eric Dolphy in His Eyes
      - Miscellany, 1989
      - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., 1988-1989, undated
    - McClain, Leanita, project, 1984-1985, undated (Box 650)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1982-1990, undated
      - Notes, 1982-1984, undated
      - Photographs, 1989, undated
      - Printed matter, 1982-1988, undated
    - Mother Courage and Her Children, 1985-1986
    - Painted Bride Art Center, Philadelphia, Pa., 1989, undated
    - The Poetry Center, San Francisco, Calif., 1989, undated
    - Ridin' the Moon in Texas, 1986, undated
    - Sassafras, Cypress, and Indigo, 1982-1989, undated, (2 folders)
    - Shapes, Sadness, and the Witch, 1983-1984, undated
    - Spell #7
      - Miscellany, 1981, 1988-1992, undated
      - Women's Playhouse Trust, London, England
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1983-1985
        - Printed matter, 1983-1985, undated
    - Sweetwater Films, 1984, undated
    - Theatre for a New Audience, New York, N.Y., 1985-1986, undated (Box 651)
    - 3 Views of Mt. Fuji, 1987, undated
    - Triptych and Bocas (formerly titled Three for a Full Moon and Bocas ), 1982-1983
    - Vive Josephine, 1987, undated
  - Shaw, Rose Tobias and Maxwell, 1962-1964
  - Sheff, Victoria, 1982-1989
  - Sheffer, Isaiah, 1986
  - Sheldon, Mary, 1977, undated
  - Shengold, Leonard
    - Correspondence and notes, 1961, 1977-1982, 1989
    - Printed matter, 1961-1979
    - Typescripts, undated
  - Sherin, Edwin, 1959-1969
  - Sherman, James, 1986
  - Shmulevich, Michael, 1986
  - Shookhoff, David, 1976-1982
  - Short, Sylvia (Box 652)
    - Contracts, 1955-1963
    - Correspondence, 1956-1964, undated
    - Notes, 1951-1964, 1979, undated
    - Photographs, 1952, undated
    - Printed matter, 1952-1959, 1969, undated
  - Shubinsky, Diane
    - Contracts, 1987-1989
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989, undated
    - Notes, 1989, undated
    - Printed matter, 1986-1988
    - Typescripts, undated
  - Shuftan, Eugen, 1955, 1964
  - Shure, Robert, 1987
  - Shute, James L., 1957-1958
  - Shutta, Ethel, 1962-1963
  - Shyre, Paul For additional material see Containers 630-631, Works about Sandburg
    - Brother to a Dragonfly, 1986, undated
    - Eugene O'Neill–A Glory of Ghosts
      - Contracts, 1984
      - Correspondence, 1982-1984
      - Notes, 1981-1987, undated
      - Printed matter, 1982-1986
      - Proposal, 1982 (Box 653)
      - Script, undated
    - Hizzoner!
      - Contracts, 1968-1974, 1982-1989, undated
      - Correspondence, 1982-1989
      - Notes, 1968-1971, 1982-1985, undated
      - Printed matter, 1984-1989
      - Script, 1983
    - I Knock at the Door, 1986-1990, undated
    - The Ladies of Odeon
      - Contracts, 1986-1987, undated, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1991, undated (Box 654)
      - Notes, 1984-1986, undated
      - Scripts, 1985, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1980-1989, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1981-1986, undated
    - Quaid-i-Azam Mohammad Ali Jinnah Commemorative Project, 1987, undated
    - Those Barrymores, 1984-1987, undated
    - U.S.A., 1987
    - Villa Serena, 1986, undated
    - Wings of Eros, 1984-1985, undated
  - Siebert, Elaine, 1957
  - Siegal, Alan P. and Robert S., 1991
  - Sigley, Marjorie, 1971-1974
  - Silverman, Eliane Leslau, 1973-1974
  - Silverstein, Karen Sperling, 1978-1984
  - Simcoe, Benjamin, 1978 (Box 655)
  - Simon, Tony, 1965-1966, undated
  - Simonton, O. Carl, 1991-1992, undated
  - Singer, Campbell, 1961 See also Containers 591-595, Ross, George
  - Singer, Lou See Container 736, Zaret, Lou
  - Singer, Reuben, 1961-1969
  - Sinkler, David, 1991-1993, undated
  - Skalicky, John (“Jan”), 1965, 1974-1975
  - Sklar, George, 1965-1966
  - Slesin, Louis, 1990-1991, undated
  - Slesin, Suzanne
    - Articles
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1978, 1989-1994
      - Notes and printed matter, 1976-1993, undated
    - Caribbean Style, 1983-1992, undated
    - English Style
      - Contracts, 1984-1989
      - Correspondence, 1982-1993
      - Notes, 1979-1985
      - Photographs and printed matter, 1982-1984
    - French Style (Box 656)
      - Contracts, 1982, 1991-1993
      - Correspondence, 1979-1984, 1992-1993
      - Galley proofs, 1981
      - Notes, 1978-1982
      - Printed matter, 1980-1982
    - Garage Cinematografica, S.R.L., 1991-1992
    - Greek Style, 1986-1989
    - Haas, Richard, book project, 1978-1980, undated
    - Indian Style, 1988-1990
    - The International Book of Lofts, 1981-1988
    - Japanese Style
      - Contracts, 1984-1985, 1991, undated
      - Correspondence, 1983-1992
      - Notes, 1983-1986
      - Printed matter, 1984-1988 (Box 657)
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1981-1995, undated
      - Notes, 1977-1992, undated
      - Printed matter, 1994-1995, undated
    - A Modern Maintenance Manual, 1985-1986
    - The New York Times Book of Modern Design Styles, Problems, and Solutions
      - Contracts, 1981-1982
      - Correspondence, 1981-1988
      - Notes and printed matter, 1981-1982
    - On Earth As It Is In Heaven, 1991-1994
    - Spanish Style, 1988-1992
  - Sloane, Allan, 1947-1948, undated
  - Slocum, William See Containers 568-569, Riccio, Vincent
  - Small, Mauri See Container 19, Beling, Stephanie
  - Smiley, Leonard V., 1975-1976, undated
  - Smith, Alison G. See Container 512, Marengo, Francesca (“Peggy”)
  - Smith, Brant See Containers 563-564, Prumbs, Lucille
  - Smith, Catherine Lee, 1977, undated
  - Smith, Charles
    - Contracts, 1991-1992
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993
    - Miscellany, 1992-1993, undated
    - Script, undated
  - Smith, Daniel Blake, 1983
  - Smith, Frederick W., 1980, undated
  - Smith, Joanna, 1972, undated
  - Smith, Lillian, 1984-1985, undated (Box 658)
  - Smith, Orde See Containers 563-564, Prumbs, Lucille
  - Smith, S. Mark, 1978-1979
  - Smith, Sally Bedell
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1979-1990, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1978-1985, undated
    - Up the Tube (formerly titled The Nineteen Inch Man )
      - Contracts, 1978-1981
      - Correspondence, 1978-1986, undated
      - Financial records, 1980-1983
      - Notes, 1978-1981, undated
      - Printed matter, 1981-1982
      - Typescripts
        - Draft, 1981, (2 folders)
        - Outlines, 1979, undated (Box 659)
  - Smith, Sara B., 1948-1950 See also Containers 563-564, Prumbs, Lucille
  - Smith, Stanley E.
    - Contract, 1958
    - Correspondence, 1958, 1966-1967
    - Notes, 1958, 1965-1968, undated
    - Printed matter, 1966, undated
  - Smithyman, Samuel David, 1976-1979
  - Snell, David
    - Contract, 1980
    - Correspondence, 1978-1981, undated
    - Financial records, 1978-1989
    - Notes, 1978-1980, undated
    - Printed matter, 1977-1979, undated
    - Typescripts, 1978, undated, (3 folders) (Box 660)
  - Solomon, Jonathan, 1991-1992
  - Spencer, Elizabeth
    - Contracts and correspondence, 1989-1992, undated
    - Notes, 1988-1989, undated
    - Photograph, undated
    - Printed matter, 1988-1989, undated
  - Spencer, Nelsie, and Laury Marker, 1992-1994, undated
  - Sperber, Ann M., 1986-1987
  - Sperdakos, George, 1979-1982 (Box 661)
  - Sperling, Carol, 1984
  - Spiegel, Steven F., and Mark Drop, 1988-1989 See also Container 105, Drop, Mark
  - Spitzer, Edwin E., 1964-1967, undated, (2 folders)
  - Spivak, Alice, undated
  - Spock, Benjamin, 1955-1960 See also Oversize
  - Stacy, Donald L., 1968-1974, undated
  - Stanley, Kim
    - The Assassination and Mrs. McKinley, 1963
    - “Ben Casey,” “A Cardinal Act of Mercy”
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1962-1966
      - Miscellany, 1962-1966, undated
    - Bus Stop
      - Box office receipts
        - Music Box Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1955
        - Other theaters, 1955
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1955
      - Miscellany, 1955-1956
      - Notes, 1954-1955, undated
      - Photographs, circa 1955 (Box 662)
      - Printed matter, 1955-1956, undated
    - “The Cake Baker,” 1960, undated
    - “CBS Playhouse,” “Secrets,” 1968, undated
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1955-1958, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1957, undated
      - Printed matter, 1958
    - The Chase, 1952, 1963, undated See also Oversize
    - Cheri
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1959, undated
      - Financial records
        - Box office receipts, 1959
        - Salary, 1959
      - Notes, 1959, undated
      - Printed matter, 1959, undated
    - A Clearing in the Woods
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1956-1957
      - Financial records, 1957
      - Miscellany, 1956-1957
      - Photographs, undated (Box 663)
    - “Dupont Show of the Month”
      - “Ethan Frome,” 1960
      - “Something to Hide,” 1963
    - “The Eleventh Hour,” 1963-1964, undated
    - Elmer Gantry, 1959, n..d.
    - A Far Country
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1960-1963
      - Financial records
        - Box office receipts, 1961, (3 folders)
        - Profit participation, 1961-1965
      - Notes, 1960-1961, undated
      - Photograph, undated
      - Printed matter, 1960-1961, undated (Box 664)
    - The Flanders Mare, 1961-1962, undated
    - Flesh and Blood
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1967
      - Miscellany, 1967-1968, undated
    - The Goddess
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1957-1961
      - Notes, 1957-1958, undated
      - Printed matter, 1957-1965, undated
    - “Goodyear Playhouse,” “Joey,” 1956
    - The Idol
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1965
      - Notes, 1965, undated
    - It's Been Wonderful, 1963-1964, undated
    - “Kraft Television Theater,” “The Glass Wall,” 1957
    - The Last Flapper, 1962-1963
    - Miscellany (Box 665)
      - Awards, 1955-1958, 1967
      - Biographical material
        - Fact sheets, undated
        - Press clippings, 1953-1979, undated
      - Contracts, 1953-1960
      - Correspondence
        - 1952-1961, (8 folders)
        - 1962-1977, (5 folders) (Box 666)
      - Deal memoranda, 1954-1956
      - Financial records
        - Accounting statements, 1955-1960, 1966, undated
        - Bills, 1955-1960, 1966-1968, undated
        - Correspondence
          - 1954-1966, (4 folders)